Hi everyone. It's Autumn, the Crafting
Enthusiast. Today, I'm going to be
kidding up my DP over product review.
And
um I have a few products here.
By the way,
welcome to my channel. You are
amazing and I thank you so much for the
support and clicking on my video. It
means the world to me that
I have the support that's like helping
me move along and um I appreciate you so
much. Thank you for
for being here and for the support. So,
um I have a few tools here that I'm
going to be using. First, I'll explain
um how I'm going to kit this up because
it it does come with these holographic
stickers,
but and
really on the canvas, it's there's 45
colors and 1 through 8 is listed as 1
through 8. So, I only used 1 through 8
on the bottles because that's the
symbol.
Um
and then then there's A through Z. And I
already had A through Z on the bottles
from my last kit, so I didn't figure it
would make any sense to take those
stickers off.
Um but this is what came with this with
this uh kit. I'll I can put a link for
these bottles down in the description. I
got them off Amazon. But if you look
right here on these stickers that came
with that, that's the ones that are on
the bottles right now.
Um okay.
Okay, so
so then
after that came the inventory sheet. So,
we have this inventory sheet. And it has
all the symbols on it right here.
Well, on the backside all for the
stickers I don't have symbols for, I
literally just cut the symbols out from
right here.
I just cut them out for the ones that I
don't have stickers for.
And then I have my Xyron sticker maker.
I can link this down below
in the description.
And
um
I'm just going to set it in there
and
pull it through.
And just you're supposed to just rub it
down like that.
And then you take off the top
part.
If I can
get that to detach.
So then you pull this off.
You're supposed to pull this off. I
don't know why it's not coming off.
Okay. So then you pull this top part off
and there you go. You have a sticker.
So I will
cut those out and stick them on the tops
of the bottles real quick.
Um
How about I go
like this?
I mean, it doesn't have to be perfect.
It just has to be able to fit on the
bottle.
And then I'm just going to trim.
I can just zoom in just a little bit.
Okay.
I'm just going to trim
like this.
I have to move the stuff in the
background
cuz
it's going to make it blurry.
Okay.
How's that? Better?
I think my camera just has decided
it's not going to work.
Okay.
So, I'm just going to um
cut the stickers.
And I'm going to sticker the bottles
real quick
with the symbols that are on here.
>> Okay, got that done.
Now that that's done, and I'm just kind
of showing you all the tools you'll need
for kitting this style up because they
do come with stickers, but not everybody
likes to kit up with number stickers and
they need the symbols. So,
in this case,
these are the symbols. So, the only
thing that's different is on the kit,
the G and the Z are backwards, which
I don't think that's going to matter to
me cuz I'm still going to know it's Z
and G.
Um
all of the all of these letters should
be right. If they're not, I just won't
use that bottle. And then I'll just
remove it and, you know,
put a blank uh an empty bottle in its
place for, you know, for the drills that
are I would try try to keep the drills
that are the bad drills, the defective
ones, and then
I keep a bottle just for themselves or
container, whatever I'm working on,
whatever kit I'm using to work on a
diamond painting,
um I save something to put the the um
defective drills in. So, this is a
little funnel that came with this kit
with these
um
bottles, with these.
>> [snorts]
>> So, I'm going to use that funnel
and
I'm going to clear off my desk real
quick cuz I don't need all this stuff on
here.
And
I'll kit this up real fast.
Okay. First of all, let's open this up.
Isn't it so pretty? I think it's
gorgeous.
Okay.
So, I do like this um canvas material. I
think it's great. It's not like
velveteen on the back or like highly
flocked or anything, but it does have
scalloped and poked edges and the cover
sheet is great and the glue is
fantastic.
The glue is awesome and the canvas feels
high quality. It's
it's nice. It's really nice. I I like
the
um
the texture of it. Okay, so these are
pre-bagged, but I don't care for working
out of bags and I honestly don't have
a um
a slotted It's fur bags. They're like a
It's like a slotted tray just for
setting bags in. Um you can get those,
but I like to kit up and I like to work
out of bottles, so I'm going to take
these
and put them in
their bottles.
So, I'm just going to
dump them out
and away I go.
Um
so, we know that number one on the
canvas is actually number one, so
I'm going to take this bottle and do
this.
I could use a tray to pour into, but I
don't think I'm going to have a problem.
We'll find out, right?
I don't think there's going to be any
static cuz these are our acrylic drills
that I could tell they were acrylic
drills.
Um but they do look really nice. So,
I'm going to put
one in the place of A in the tray
because one is the very first thing on
the
um
on the canvas.
Um I'm going to switch the first row. I
need two.
All right.
And then that's just how the kitting
process is going to go up.
If I did put down a tray, put a tray
down for for this for pouring drills,
it would probably make it a little bit
easier.
And I wouldn't be losing losing any
drills.
Here's another thing I love about these
bottles is they're big enough to hold
a lot of drills. So, if I need a second
one, I know I have more.
This one is number five. I think there's
two number fives. So, we'll Let's see
how much we can get in one
bottle. How much of these drills we can
fit in one of these bottles.
So, this one is
I I want to say these are
a measurement right here, 25.8.
I think that's the weight.
I believe that's the weight.
So, I got
one bag in there and it's a little bit
more than half. Let's see if I can get
the second bag in.
I don't know if we're going to be able
to.
If I get it all in, it'll be right at
the very top.
Like literally, there's only a couple
left.
So,
I'll probably
>> [snorts]
>> be playing a balancing act.
So, in theory, yes, two full bags did
fit in a bottle.
>> [laughter]
>> It worked. Okay.
So, that's kind of cool to know.
So, that's 25.8
something. I don't know what's the
measurement. It's not in ounces, it's in
I don't know.
Okay.
Number six.
I'm just making sure they match cuz who
wants to put the wrong drills in with
the wrong symbol, right?
>> [clears throat]
>> This is so pretty. I'm so excited to
work on it.
I have a couple images images that I was
working on making and I would really
like to
um send them in to DP over to have them
turned into diamond paintings.
And
I actually have several.
This is number eight.
And I love that DP over allows you to be
the artist, you know.
I think that's great. And you're the
artist, you get to create designs
and then send them to them and they turn
them into diamond paintings for you. I
love that.
And everybody gets a chance to be an
artist. We're not all perfect, so we
let, you know, AI can
perfect in the sense of hey, you know, I
I'm not a great artist, but I would
really like to have a diamond painting
that looks like, you know,
something
um
something that I would like to work on,
you know, not someone else's design, but
my own.
So it allows us to be our an artist. So
I'm going to organize these real fast
cuz they're not in order.
I'm going to have to
I'm just putting them in order.
And I like that the letters and the
numbers are all in
um alphabetical order.
Or sorry, numerical and alphabet
alphabetic order.
So
if I do this, I know it's maybe not
making sense, but if I do this, then
everything
will be in order, and I can just take
from here.
Cuz I got all of these ones done, so I'm
going to take from here, and A
is number nine.
So, the numbers are on the bags right
here.
So,
11, 12, 13. Okay.
And maybe I'll grab a tray.
Just grab a tray to work on.
Then if some spill out, it's in the
tray, you know.
Ooh, what the world?
Got a head shaker here, I think.
Oh, if you hear noise in the background,
my son's home from work. He's not
working today, and
they're out there gaming with their
friends online, so
they're having fun.
B is
number
Actually, there is no B. So, I'm going
to take that one out. It jumps to C.
Okay.
So, number 10 is C. Good thing I checked
the legend, right?
Um
>> D is 11.
But if you don't like to kit up, you can
always go ahead and just you you know,
these come free bags. Just get one of
those slotted
bag trays.
They're slotted trays just for working
out of bags.
E
Oh, there's no E. Okay, I'm going to
take that one out. How about F? There is
an F.
And that one is number 12. Okay.
Pay attention. Pay attention to this
legend on the side here cuz that's
what's really helping me not make a
mistake.
And then the G, I know the G is
backwards, but that's okay cuz I'm not
going to make a mistake in that.
739, that's it.
I mean this kitting process might take a
second just because I'm really paying
attention to the legend.
If it gets too complicated and I can't
talk through it, then I'll just add
music and speed it up.
H
There's no I either. I'll take the I
out.
So, H is
number 14. Okay.
This little funnel is really nice. like
that it's aluminum.
I like because I don't think anything's
going to stick to it. Like even if there
were
uh if there was um
static, I don't think it would stick to
it. Okay.
J
J is number 15.
So, if it does take me a second to get
this up, that's why. It's I'm really
paying attention to the
to the legend.
J K is number 16.
And of course, I got to make a mess
because that's what I do.
Okay.
L
Yep, there's an L. That's number 17.
So, how was your guys' day?
What are you doing today? Do you have
plans this weekend? It's kind of getting
to be the end of the summer and school
starting here
in in this town, school's starting on
the 20th of
of August.
I can't believe it's starting that
early. It seems that seems a little bit
early. We didn't start school till after
Labor Day when I was
when I was a kid. L M
And here they're starting in some places
the 20th of August or the 20th right
around the 20th through the 25th.
I just think that's really early.
Maybe maybe they're wanting summer to
get out or school to get out a little
earlier in the year. I don't know.
But
N is 814.
Ooh, there's a lot in this one.
That's number 19. Okay, let's I bet you
I can get this whole bag in here.
This is a lot.
Nice. I love that color, too. It's like
a brick red. It's very pretty.
I wonder if that goes in the center of
the flower.
Yep, it does. It goes in here. This is a
bit of confetti. Not bad. I don't think
it's bad. It's more like checkerboarding
in here.
Um
to cause that color gradient.
N
Ooh.
number 20
Ooh, there's a lot of that one, too.
Um my son, his YouTube channel's doing
really, really good. He put out a video
the other day and
uh it's like 2 days ago and it's reached
um
over 4,000 views.
So, and he just started his channel. Um
I'll link it. I can link link his
channel down below. And look at that.
It's right at the top.
In the
um description box, but it's all about
dirt biking and stuff like that. So,
and mountain biking. He does mountain
biking, too.
Trails. He does trails around
um Colorado and Montana and Utah. Let's
see. Is this number 21? Yeah.
Um they go riding on all sorts of trails
in all the different states. So,
if you guys want to go show him some
support, give him a subscribe,
you know. But, I mean,
I know that he really wants people that
are going to actually watch his video. A
2 4 is our number 22.
Um
but it's really awesome how good he's
doing and I'm it's awesome.
S
um
There's no S.
Okay.
T
8 9 1 T number 23.
But,
I don't know if I did I say that this is
from DP over? This is my product review
from DP over.
And I just did an unboxing of it.
And
um I wanted to just keep going and start
working on it.
Let's see. U
24? Yes.
>> [clears throat]
>> Not really a a much else going on. I
know my husband wanted to go camping
this weekend, so I mean it still might
happen. It's only Wednesday, so
it still might happen.
And um he's found a campground that a
lot of people are very happy with.
Number 25.
26.
Okay, so 27's going to be probably
need two bottles cuz that's a lot of
that color.
I don't know. When we go camping, I
always get like, "Okay, what am I going
to take to work on?" I always got to
take something. I can't just go camping.
I have to take something to work on like
in the evenings to relax, to
um I just love it. Um my cross stitch, I
take my cross stitch, I take um a
diamond painting like a mini kit diamond
painting.
Um the mini dazzles or something from
Diamond Art Club.
It's Y. Is there a Y?
Why is number 27? And I think I need two
of those.
And I'm kind of wondering if there is I
can just grab
I'm just going to grab another one off
of here.
It came with this.
That way
I have two bottles labeled the same.
Okay.
It's a nice thing that came the stickers
came with the kit. So
All right.
Put those
Okay,
let's see how much this is. This is
35.8.
So, that's a weight on the scale.
Okay, so we get one bag in here.
Yeah, it's definitely going to take two
bags.
Okay, so my sister came over today
and my neighbor
Oh, it's so sweet. My neighbor gave her
a pick of the litter out of her net last
litter of pups
and
my sister chose one and she was
surprising the kids today.
Um, she was came to pick up the puppy.
It was ready to go home. She came to
pick up the puppy and
take it home and it was I'm just really
excited to see how
how the kids react. So, she was going to
do like a Snapchat, I think.
Cuz I wanted to see their reaction.
And
it's just awesome.
So, that little puppy is so cute. Oh my
gosh, she wanted to cuddle and
>> [laughter]
>> what do you do? You just got to cuddle
them.
Number 30.
Almost got this done already.
So, um I'll probably just have this be
the kitting up process and kind of show
you how I'm doing this because and it
doesn't didn't come with symbol
stickers. So, that's why I took them off
of the inventory sheets. I just cut the
symbols off the inventory sheets and
then figured that would be
good enough. This is a plus sign and
this is number 31.
And this has a lot of
specials in it.
They're so pretty.
Okay, after the plus sign is the equal
sign.
And that one is number 32.
And to know what I'm kitting, you know,
how you like how do you know what you
kit this kit up in and have so many
Yeah, so I'll just like cut this section
out and put it in here and that way I
know that this this goes with this.
Um
but, you know, I mean
that's just kind of how I do it.
I try to keep the
the um cut the picture if it comes with
a a sh-
What do you What do you call it? Like a
sticker sheet and it's the picture on
the sticker sheet is a sticker, I'll
just put it in here.
So, I'm
I'm going to move these
down.
Okay, we're on lower
A.
That one is number 34.
Um
So, after this, I think
I'm going to probably
kit up my feel it.
I do have one that's I'm that I'm almost
done with. I actually need to just sit
down and work on that.
Number 35.
And get that one done. And then I'm only
one feel it behind after that.
Cuz this does have static in it. This
one does.
So,
yeah, I'm only one feel it behind. Then
after that, I only got to get blooms
done.
And then I'm literally like done.
And I'm caught up. And then I can work
on this month's T.
T is number 36.
Okay. And then
I'll take one of these. Arrow.
Number 37.
I'm almost done.
I did have to kind of pay attention on
this
while I was kitting up because I was
literally
like thinking, "Oh, no, I got to pay
attention to the legend." Cuz
some of them where the bottles are
marked, some of them are not on the
sticker sheet. They're not on the
legend.
38. This is
quite a few of these.
White.
Okay.
And that's 39. Okay, now we're down to
the specials. So, 39 is an AB.
It's so pretty. Um it's AB
445.
And then
Okay, this one is full now. Look at how
pretty that looks. Isn't that look
pretty? Let me put the lid on it.
I'm going to put the lid on it and then
I'll tip it upside down and you can see
all the colors from the bottom. I think
you'll be able to.
Ooh, they're pretty. Look at that.
That's very pretty.
Okay.
So, there's that one. And now I've got
I'll [snorts] just finish this one real
quick.
Okay, this one is number 40.
This one is um I did not choose this
size. This size was chosen for me by DP
over and it's a 65 by 50 cm.
There's only been a little bit of static
in one of them. Otherwise, and it could
be caused from the plastic bag.
This one,
42.
Ooh, this one's got a lot of static in
it. Oh my.
This one's got a lot of static in it.
I'm going to have to put that a tray
under it or something.
Let me see.
I do have my static guard and I got
dryer sheets, so if I need to
They're coming out slowly.
I do not know if they're acrylic drills.
I I don't think I don't think these ones
are acrylic. I think the specials
are resin.
The specials are resin, you guys. These
These
uh
Um I could tell that the other ones were
acrylic, but these ones are resin.
And that's probably why they're so I
didn't think they were going to stick to
metal.
Hm, interesting.
Anyway, maybe I'll get a dryer sheet and
stick a dryer sheet in there.
I feel like they're jumping out of the
bottle.
It's like, "No.
>> [gasps]
>> You can't make me go in there."
I I swear they were jumping out of the
bottle.
Okay, there's one more. Sorry, guys. My
battery went dead.
I don't know if you how long it was
while it was dead.
I wasn't paying attention. I wasn't even
looking.
I need to pay more attention to that cuz
it does that to me. It'll just either
stop recording
at the 30-minute mark or it will just go
dead. So, okay.
Um I got everything kitted up in my
bottles. Oh, there's another lid. Where
did I put it?
It's down here. Okay. [laughter]
There.
And I'm just going to take this and
stick it in the top right here
of this one.
Like that. And that way I know
what
um
what this kit goes to. So, okay. So,
that's my kit up of this one from DP
over. They were generous enough to let
me choose
um on the website what I would like what
design I would like and they chose the
size for me and I think it is very very
generous.
So,
um yeah.
So, I hope I didn't miss too much of the
kitting up process. I don't know because
my battery went dead. But, it's kitted
up now and I'm going to do
uh I think I'm going to kit up
mhm I might just do an unboxing and then
um do a diamond uh cross stitch. So, I
don't know what I'm going to do. I'm
confused.
>> [laughter]
[gasps]
>> Thank you for spending your time with
me. I hope you enjoyed the video and
even though I was struggling, um I
probably could have made it easier by
getting a dryer sheet. It would have
been a way easier. But,
I'm done now and I hope you guys, you
know, are spending your time where you
loved and appreciated because your time
is valuable. You're the only you. There
is no one to replace you.
So, no one else like you on this whole
earth. So, you are valuable. Your time
is valuable. Spend it where you are
loved and appreciated. Okay.
I'll see you on the next one. Bye.